Guide to the Suite 13, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Suite 13, Yale University, records
2000-2004
RU 959
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(1 box)
The records consist of administrative files, scripts, and publicity flyers for the productions of Suite 13 at Yale.
Suite 13
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 40 (YRG 40), Records of Yale clubs, societies, and organizations.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from Suite 13, 2004.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Biographical / Historical
Suite 13, a student group that performed sketch comedy, was founded at Yale in 2000 and disbanded in 2006.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files, scripts, and publicity flyers for the productions of Suite 13 at Yale.
College students -- Societies, etc.; College theater; Comedy sketches; Theater; Suite 13; Yale University -- Societies, etc.; Yale University -- Students
- Production records, 2000-2004; Accession 2004-A-183
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - Pranks, press, and administrative records, 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - first show, Winter 2001 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Second Cumming, Spring 2001 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - extrava-CUM-ganza!, Fall 2001 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - spec-EATMYDICK-tacular!, Winter 2002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cock Riot!, Spring 2002 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Vagina Hat!, Fall 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gay Bash!, Winter 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Suite 13 Is the Best Comedy Group at Yale, Spring 2003 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Coke Nite, Fall 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Suite 13 Fucks You with Our Cock!, Winter 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Legend: The Legendary Legend of the Suite 13 Legend, Spring 2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)